Unreleased version from the year 2023.
Translation, subtitles, timing, and correction: Ander Innervideo.
NG Knight Ramune and 40 DX
Saying goodbye is difficult after all
A smile is the best thing you can give!
Don't let it get to you.
I will keep moving forward.
I don't know what tomorrow will be like.
The path of solitude
Is the destiny of the hero.
Welcome high school girls (high school girls!)
Welcome college girls (college girls!)
To the East, West, North, South, right, and left! (let's go!)
Please wait for my arrival.
If this world is a great game
I promise you a happy ending.
If your level is low
Don't worry about it.
The romance of our previous life wasn't bad either
One life at a time
Or they will accumulate.
You shine brightly, my lady (my lady!)
Like a office lady too (OL too!)
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday too, (Friday too!)
I will fight 24 hours.
Be careful with the double reserve! (be careful!)
If you fail, I'll see my blood run (I'll see blood!)
To the East, West, North, South, right, and left! (We're going to win!)
My youth is my sin.
We couldn't miss the opportunity to get the three sacred sisters!
This will make things easier for us, sister.
Where am I?
You seem to have a lot of energy.
What is all this about?
What are you doing?
And who are you, and why are you treating us like this?
Good morning, did you sleep well?
You are the ones from the crystal ball.
Oh, how do you know?
You looked so defenseless while sleeping, and to think that
you are the three sacred sisters.
How do you know?
Even if you don't know, we have a shared relationship and history.
I don't like how you're saying it.
What are you going to do to us?
You better release us, or you'll pay dearly.
We can't do that.
Your power is now part of our plan.
Plan?
Our mission is to make our father's dreams come true.
We will take control of the Doki Doki Space.
That's it!
Don Harumage.
Exciting space-time, fiery battle.
Warriors of love forever.
Finally, finally we have arrived.
I'm so excited right now.
When you think about it, it was a tremendous path of difficulties and suffering.
My indomitable spirit can overcome any obstacle.
Gold-Chan, Silver-Chan, I'm coming right now.
I'll give you my entire body.
Here come the brave warriors.
We need to test if they meet
the warrior standard we need.
Lamunes.
Da Cider.
You're an idiot.
Look, sister.
Do they both seem familiar to me?
Indeed...
Apparently, they are not them.
It seems they are second-rate warriors.
Despicable.
Wretched.
We have to get out of here somehow, mya.
But how?
There's only one way.
And it's like this, mya.
Alright.
So, let's make them put in some effort.
What is this?
I can't stop thinking about them.
Well, these are obstacles to glory.
I'm surprised at how well they're doing.
Great.
Lamunes, what are you doing?
Actually, Da Cider, you're a fool.
The goal is near.
One step closer to glory.
Damn you, Lamunes.
Da Cider, don't move.
Lamunes.
Da Cider.
It tickles.
If we move, it will be our end.
That butterfly was incredibly ticklish.
Astro yoyo.
We survived this time.
I thought I was going to die.
Where am I?
Mr. Lamunes.
Leska, don't do that in front of others.
Leave that alone, Da Cider.
What are you doing?
I'm tired of you attacking me by surprise.
Where are we?
That hurts.
This isn't a dream.
Why don't you shave your balls?
Welcome, brave warriors!
You've passed all the tests.
I am Gold Mountain.
I am Silver Mountain.
Fine ladies, I am the famous Lamu...
Beautiful ladies.
This body is tougher than a wall,
I am the brave Da Ci...
You scoundrel! What are you doing?
I was here before you.
You want to fight?
Let's do it.
You two, stop that fight.
Then, allow us to attend to you.
That's right.
Fighting gets us nowhere...
Why are they behaving like this?
Lamunes is a complete idiot.
Da Cider, you detestable otaku.
How are you?
It's delicious.
Paradise, paradise.
But what can we do for you?
Well, leave it all to this glorious body.
Well, you're making noise like a big boat in a mud tank.
What?
Don't argue, please!
Now then, it's time to fulfill your desires...
Don't think about anything else, okay?
Lamunes. —Da Cider.
What was that?
Is this a hallucination?
What's going on?
No, nothing's wrong.
If we scorn them...
—we would be a disgrace.
Lamunes, you're a big idiot.
Da Cider, you despicable scoundrel.
Miruku, please forgive me, I'm sorry.
Leska, I was wrong, spare my life.
Is this another hallucination?
Gold-chan. —Silver-chan.
Don't talk to us with that confidence.
Hey, hey. You guys are the Heroes Lamunes and Da Cider.
Why are they suddenly acting like this?
Suddenly, their attitudes have changed.
It seems like a joke.
What's going on?
Silence. —Silence.
Both of you are enemies of our father.
Enemies of your father?
Wait.
What's happening?
Where are we?
Lamunes.
Da Cider.
Oh! Seinaru Miruki, Seinaru Cacao, Seinaru Lemon.
Why are you in this place?
Lamunes, haven't you realized yet?
It's me.
You are Miruku.
In that case, you must be Leska?
Now you know, you idiot!
So the other one is Cocoa?
But why did you do this, Miruku?
Leskar, do you have those hobbies?
Of course not.
We did it to capture them.
Capture us?
Anyway, release us quickly.
Don't even think about it, Lamunes. —Da Cider.
You've fooled us well!
Are you trying to undermine our ambition
by pretending to be warriors we recruited?
I don't know what you're talking about.
—A play on words?
We're ready.
What do you say?
That's Don Harumage.
Who are you?
We are the maidens of the Goburiki sanctuary.
Our mission is to fulfill
the ambitions of our lord Goburiki.
We won't stand for the enemies
of our father Gokuriki!
Priestesses of Goburiki?
Consider us as enemies?
Don't say such things.
Yes, yes, let's stop arguing.
Shut up.
We will crush them in an instant.
Waku Waku Space-Time activated.
Waku Waku Space-Time?
Look at that.
This is a prototype of the King Squasher
that we have revived thanks to the power
accumulated from many warriors.
This is the prototype of Queen Sideron.
This will take them out.
Prototype King Squasher.
Prototype Queen Sideron.
The problem is that we've used
our power in all the fights
and incidents during the journey.
Now we're in danger.
We have to...
—Defeat them.
The power of hundreds of warriors we've gathered so far.
It will serve to crush both of them.
Die!
Damn, it's useless without King Squasher.
That's right. I don't have Queen Sideron either.
Ready, mya. —My dear.
Lamunes. —Tama Q.
Darling —Hebi Metaco.
With you, Tama Q, we'll win.
Let's go, Tama Q.
OK, mya.
OK, Heavy Metaco, us too.
Heavy Metaco.
King Squasher.
Queen Sideron.
Let's go.
I will.
Lamunes.
Da Cider.
Tama Q, what the heck is a prototype King Squasher?
I once heard that in ancient times
there was a military protectorate...
and they created experimental prototypes.
Those must have been the prototypes
for King Squasher and Queen Sideron.
They have the same power as ours, mya.
The only thing left to do is
to rely on the skill of the pilot.
Then victory will belong to my dear.
Shut up.
There's a way to prove it.
Royal Straight Flush.
Da Cider, let's use the Royal Scratch.
OK.
I'm burning fiercely now.
Switching to Samurai On mode.
In that case, I have to...
Yay! Da Cider, you're a simpleton.
You look like a child.
You're an idiot!
Nerd, clumsy, weirdo.
Come on... Your word games are boring.
Fool, imbecile...
What do you say, bastards?
Go to hell.
Panther Mode activated.
Royal Scratch.
Shit, what happened?
They are absorbing the power of the three sacred sisters, mya.
Then I have to rescue Miruku.
That's right, mya.
Damn it.
Lamunes.
Da Cider.
What was that?
The Giant Ship 320 Rocket Ho.
Princesses.
We've come to the rescue.
Seyrom, Assam.
Please, leave it to us.
Danger, stand back.
What is this?
Why do you think you can just leave?
We'll send you to the other world.
Now!
I'll rescue Leska.
That's what you get for boasting.
Sister, the power isn't enough.
¿Do you think we'll let them go?
Royal Straight Flush.
We have trouble, Mya.
Tama Q, please take charge for a moment.
Hebi Metako, take charge too.
Wait, darling.
Lamunes.
Da Cider.
Miruku, are you okay?
Because you've done something so dangerous.
Hello, Leska.
Don't play dumb; you didn't have to worry about me.
Lamunes, I can't hold on any longer.
Honey, quickly.
Cocoa is still sleeping.
Hold on, Miruku.
As you say, Lamunes.
OK.
Hey, Leska.
Tell me, Da Cider.
Have you gained weight?
Don't be reckless.
Lamunes —Honey.
We only have one chance.
Get ready for the jump.
OK.
Royal Scratch.
Sister, power is not enough.
What happened to the power of the three sacred sisters?
We've put an end to that conspiracy.
Our mission is complete, Lamunes.
I slept so well.
My glasses.
Cocoa, you're finally opening your eyes.
Hey, you guys.
What have you done!
You've even destroyed the Puff Puff Palace.
Oh, those girls are still alive!
How resistant.
We can't forgive them.
We're going to kill those beasts.
Cursed ones, this won't be forgotten.
We'll get our revenge next time.
The last time-space stone still remained.
It seems they have reconciled.
Have you received your punishment?
Ah, I remembered.
You've been deceiving us from the start.
No, I mean...
Well, you see...
I'll punish you. —I'll punish you.
I hope they learn their lesson. —They'll learn.
There won't be a second time.
It won't happen again.
No objections.
Okay, okay, I'll call the Arara Castle and ask them to pick us up.
Ara-ra.
I am Princess Lyria of the Muchi Muchi Kingdom.
Now we need strong warriors in our kingdom.
I'll reward you with the best I have.
I'll be waiting.
Da Cider.
Lamunes.
Let's go to the Muchi Muchi Kingdom...
What are you doing? You haven't learned your lesson at all.
Ara ara.
Ara?
Timing, encoding, and multiplexing by: Ander Innervideo.
NG Knight Ramune and 40 DX OVA Ending 2
Triple Romance.
Asphalt Rain.
Pianissimo Night.
I perched on the window and dreamed under the moonlight.
I can't go back.
Holding a blanket.
In the middle of a kiss.
Don't get attached to me!
Cruel reality, I can't keep my promise.
I'll run away from you too.
I am my three sisters at the same time.
A story of love for love.
Heartless, triple romance
Heartless, triple romance.