Unreleased version from 2023.
Translation, subtitles, timing, and correction: Ander Innervideo.
Hello, I'm the brave Lamunes in trouble again...
In the Hara Hara world, the Gold and Silver Mountain sisters
ask for help from powerful warriors.
Da Cider and I are traveling
to the Puff Puff palace in the Ura Ura valley.
However, besides us,
a number of challenging warriors have appeared.
What will happen?
Even more, a trio of mysterious and cute warriors
appeared and exposed our weaknesses.
This journey has become a mess.
I hope everything turns out fine!
Gold-Chan, Silver-Chan, wait for me.
I'm feeling so excited!
When will you stop doing that?
NG Knight Ramune and 40 DX
Saying goodbye is difficult after all.
A smile is the best thing you can give!
Don't let it affect you.
I will keep moving forward.
I don't know what tomorrow will bring.
The path of solitude.
It's the destiny of the hero.
Welcome, high school girls (high school girls!)
Welcome, college girls (college girls!)
To the East, West, North, South, right and left! (let's go!)
Please wait for my arrival.
If this world is a big game,
I promise you a happy ending.
If your level is low,
Don't worry about it.
The romance of our previous life wasn't bad either.
One life at a time,
Or they'll keep accumulating.
You look impressive, my lady (my lady!)
Like a office lady too (OL too!)
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, even Friday (even Friday!)
I will fight 24 hours.
Beware of the double reserve! (be careful!)
If you fail, I'll see my blood run (I'll see blood!)
To the East, West, North, South, right and left! (Let's win!)
My youth is my sin.
Exciting space-time, fiery battle.
Warriors of love from the past.
Miruku, Cocoa
Darling, Leska
Where is everyone? da-mya.
Hebi.
Tomb to the tombs!
What?
What are you up to?
Hurry up and do something, Da Cider.
Wake up.
What's wrong with you?
You're doing all this
because Don Harumage brainwashed you.
Wait a minute, I don't remember doing that.
More and more of that, more.
That's my motto (mottoda)
See, you're the only one making such stupid puns.
Don't get carried away.
Da Cider, why are you doing this?
What?!
Lamunes, you can't distinguish my self from my other self.
More, destroy more.
It's your fault.
Stop blaming me, I don't know what's happening either.
Yahooo.
I've found you, Lamunes. - Good to see you, Da Cider.
Where did they come from?
Wait. - Don't go.
Wait.
Hey! Lamunes, this way.
Oh! They went that way.
By the way, where are we?
King Squasher.
What are you doing?
I told you I don't know, idiot!
What?
Miruku, don't you think this situation is strange?
I can't think about that now,
I must focus on hitting them.
Well said.
- But...
Are we time traveling?
- Yes.
The collision of the rocks caused an explosion in the cave
And we've fallen into the Hara Hara world from three years ago.
In other words, we're now in a different time.
But how did you reach that conclusion?
Your head's going to explode.
Can't you acknowledge I'm right without disrespecting me?
So, how do we return to the original time?
With an explosion.
If we get caught in an explosion like last time.
Something like this.
What?
The solution.
(Note: a play on words between rubbing, butt, and solution).
I can't keep relying on him.
Come on, Lamunes, we can't let King Squasher see us.
Dimensional explosion stone?
What's that?
This is...
If this explodes, we'll time travel.
Why do you have something so dangerous?
Because... it's weird.
Hurry up, Lamunes.
Please wait.
What has happened?
This shouldn't have happened.
And that...
That was dangerous.
The danger isn't over yet.
Miruki Sword, action.
And now where are we?
That's the Star Ship.
(Note: they have fallen to chapter 11 of the first season.)
Oh, just what we needed.
Great! Let's ride that thing.
Yahoo!
What?
Is no one here?
They're the 8 Pawn siblings.
What's wrong with the Pawn siblings?
Hey, Lamunes, make them stop.
So, how do we get back?
I've tried to investigate,
but the components of these rocks are unknown.
One of these rocks will take us to the present.
Which one is it?
I don't know.
If we explode them one by one?
We might get trapped in the time-space forever.
Wait a moment.
Miruku, I know
They haven't received their punishment yet.
Then, let's leave returning to the present for later.
Let's do the Cocoa transformation.
Seinaru Milky Power.
Seinaru Lemon Power.
Seinaru Cacao Power.
Transformation. —Transformation
Hurry up.
Don't look at me.
I am a royal warrior who fights
for love and justice, Seinaru Miruki.
And I am Seinaru Lemon.
I am Cacao.
Lamunes —Da Cider.
We will punish them.
They're not here anymore.
What's wrong with these guys?
Oh, I remember now.
We're in the port city.
Oh, I remember, this is where
we met Mart Ross.
People used to fight in the streets over that drink.
We found them.
Don't move.
Let's flee.
Just in time.
Lamunes, it's not time to celebrate.
Right, wait.
Sorry.
Wait.
My glasses.
Here...
Thank you.
Oh, you're so kind, sister.
Oh, how sweet you are.
Wearing glasses is such a shame, don't you think?
Excuse me, I'm in a hurry.
Yes, see you another time.
Yes, take care.
It's time for...
—You to give up.
You need time to make me surrender.
Toki (time) says to give up.
I thought of something too.
You realize something stupid
after doing something stupid!
What is this?
Oh, Da Cider.
These are the explosion rocks that threw us through time-space.
What?
I see...
(Note: they have traveled to chapter 16 of the first season.)
Soy sauce.
Guys.
You wouldn't dare?
We might!
Don't do it.
You know well what will happen to you if you do.
How foolish.
These girls think they know us well, Lamunes.
But there's something they don't know.
What?
That's right, you don't know how Miruku gets.
Leska too.
What do you mean?
We're not afraid of any consequences.
That's why we act without thinking.
That's right, I even started to enjoy the fights.
This is a testimony from two brave Warriors.
Do it, Da Cider.
This place...
(Note: they have traveled to chapter 16 of the first season.)
Yes, this is the great floating tree in the forest.
beppin should be somewhere
I'm hungry.
You sound like a little girl.
Yoo...
Oh, oh.
I just have to wait for them to arrive.
Yahoo.
What are you all doing here?
It's been a long time...
Leska, how did you get here so quickly?
We're chasing Lamunes and his partner.
What?
This can't be, but on the monitor...
I'm sorry, could you give us something to eat?
Huh?
Come on, we're old friends.
No problem... You look a bit older.
Leave me alone.
Where are we?
Well, I've seen this scene somewhere before.
I bought an FD BOX for cases like these,
I think I have it stored here.
Alright, but...
Aren't you hungry?
Now that you mention it, I'm feeling hungry... (hetta naa)
Head head, double head.
Again with the same thing.
Oh, we have a lot of apples here.
Why are you dressed like that?
You look like you're going to a comic convention!
Aren't you too old for that?
How sad that you have to resort to this to appear young.
Soon you'll have wrinkles.
Are you looking for a fight?
I've eaten well.
Sister, remember why we came here.
I know.
Sister?
Ah, we've been separated for a long time
but they are my sisters.
We're after Lamunes and his partner.
Thank you for the food.
Come on, let's go.
Where are you going?
What?
What is that idiot doing?
Leska, your friend has changed.
I don't know what you're talking about, what was that?
But if... that was Da Cider, sister.
Idiot.
So that was your beloved Da Cider.
You sure have bad taste.
No, it's a misunderstanding.
How strange.
That face, that personality, and those unpleasant phrases
As well as his pumpkin head, how can you not love that man...
What?
I was wondering, which of his qualities attracted you the most?
Stop bothering, you're the least qualified to talk about men.
Well, love has affected you, unbelievable.
You've made me angry, you're dead.
How funny, try it.
There are many princesses gathered here.
What a shame.
Both have been eating mulberries and turned into fairy tale characters.
Let's dance with the princesses.
This is the most suitable boyfriend for you.
Cocoa, how can we return these two to their original state?
If they eat the "original" fruit that looks like blue apples, it's at the top of the tree.
Let's dance!
Pair of fools.
Don't be embarrassed anymore.
What were we doing?
What a strange dream I had for listening to you and eating that.
Idiot, what are you basing that on to blame me.
What are you saying?
Even if they return to normal, they behave the same way.
I am Gold Mountain. - I am Silver Mountain.
Da Cider. - Lamunes.
This is not the time to fight.
We have a great mission.
Now we need to return to the present.
Let's go back.
Damn it.
That was strange.
At least those two are there.
I won't forgive them.
Where are we? - Here they are.
(Note: Chapter 36.)
Damn it.
Oh, it can't be.
This way we'll never be able to go back.
Those are...
Missiles. - Missiles.
What was all that?
Where are we?
Are you alright?
They don't seem to be hurt.
Dammit. Involving innocent people in battle.
I'll never forgive them. Syder.
I agree. Ramune.
I'm feeling very furious now.
Ah, he looks like Lamunes.
What's going on?
They are the first Legendary warriors.
But that was a long time ago, right?
Well, about 5000 years ago.
Please stay here.
You need to stay away from me.
I'm fine.
Please, heroes, can we go with you?
We cannot allow it.
We don't want to get involved in the fight.
We've been traveling with three women.
But now they are in the hands of the enemy, in that castle.
It's all our fault!
We brought them to this dangerous place.
I wish those two would behave like true heroes.
You're right.
We fell into a dangerous place.
I don't recognize this place.
This is the Ura Ura Valley!
We finally arrived.
Let's hurry to get to the Puff Puff Palace.
If they're here, we can't do anything.
Can we help you with something?
Don't worry, we'll take care of the rest!
Of course.
Aren't they wonderful?
Come on, Syder.
We need to rescue Miruku and the girls.
Yes.
Ramune.
You, what do you feel for Miss Miruku?
Of course I love her.
Mr. Syder, do you also love Miss Cafeore?
So, take care.
They're wonderful.
Why weren't we born in this era?
We're forgetting our original purpose.
Those two.
Da Cider, the Puff Puff Palace
looks more like a castle.
We definitely have to go.
Gold-Chan, wait for me. - Silver-Chan, I'm coming.
Wait there.
We can't forgive...
Men who trample on women's feelings.
We will punish them in the name of love and justice.
The warrior princesses
Are here.
Have they been there all this time?
Shut up.
We'll punish them.
Time to escape.
Wait.
I'll be the first to reach the Puff Puff Palace.
Don't even think about it.
You guys. - Wait.
Da Cider, are those Kings Squasher and Queen Sideron?
Still not back to the present?
Don't forget about us!
Where do you think you're going!
Oh, wait.
Wow, what a surprise.
Miruku, Cocoa. - Sister Leska, you're alive.
Who's there, da-mya?
We sensed the presence of a sacred power.
What good luck.
We've encountered the three sacred sisters.
Where are we? Have we returned to the present?
Oh! Da Cider.
What?
Puff Puff Palace.
Da Cider.
Well, this time seems to be the right one.
Let's go.
Yaho, yaho, la, la, yaho la, la.
The same thing happened 5000 years ago.
But sister, this time the purpose is different.
That's right.
We're going to use the power of the three sacred sisters.
To increase our strength.
And conquer the Doki Doki Space.
Yaho, yaho, la, la, yaho la, la.
Yaho, la, la...
Time, encoding, and multiplexing by: Ander Innervideo.
NG Knight Ramune and 40 DX Ending 1 V2
Lullaby ☆ My Dear.
Why are my breasts peach-colored?
Why is your hand bigger? Why?
Coincidentally, both sizes fit perfectly.
Like a natural scent that overlays any perfume.
GOOD NIGHT, my heart.
GOOD NIGHT, Good night.
Like a lullaby whisper (Lullaby)
GOOD NIGHT, before falling asleep.
GOOD NIGHT, if you dream.
And so the ecstasy will feel, ah, ah...