Unreleased version from the year 2023.
Translation, subtitles, timing, and correction: Ander Innervideo.
It looks like Cocoa,
I can do it.
I'll leave it like that.
What could it have been?
Hello!
Waaa!
You!
Long time no see, Lamunes.
Da Cider, why do you appear so suddenly?
Wait, I just came to annoy you for a moment.
I hope I'm not causing any trouble.
Has something happened in the Hara Hara world?
Actually, there's something I want to show you.
What is this?
I am Gold Mountain.
I am Silver Mountain.
We are the Mountain Dew sisters.
Wow, how cute!
Thanks to the warriors for receiving this message.
We beg you to please help us.
What?
Our mission is to keep an ancient evil sealed.
But our power is not enough.
Therefore, we seek powerful people
to help us in this mission.
What?
In return, you will be rewarded.
We are willing to please you as much as we can.
What?
What!?
Please, come and help us at the Puff Puff Palace.
We won't disappoint you.
Da-da-da Cider, what does this mean?
I had a lot of difficulties (fights)
to get this strange crystal orb.
Da Cider, why exactly are you showing me this?
Well, keep watching.
Please, all the warriors
come when you hear our call.
We need each warrior.
To each...?
I am Gold.
I am Silver.
We need two perfect warriors; we will be
at the Puff Puff Palace in the Ura Ura Valley.
Da Cider, we have to go and help them!
Aren't we men?
That's the spirit, Lamunes.
I'm feeling that...
...I'm burning with excitement.
Alright, we have to leave.
Let's go!
NG Knight Ramune and 40 DX.
Saying goodbye is difficult after all.
A smile is the best thing you can give!
Don't let that affect you.
I will keep moving forward.
I don't know what tomorrow will bring.
The path of loneliness.
Is the fate of the hero.
Welcome, high school girls (high school girls!)
Welcome, college girls (college girls!)
Towards the East, West, North, South, right, and left! (Let's go!)
Please wait for my arrival.
If this world is a big game.
I promise you a happy ending.
If your level is low.
Don't worry about it.
Our romance from our past lives wasn't bad either.
One life at a time.
Or they will accumulate.
You look impressive, my lady (my lady!)
Like a office lady too (OL too!)
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, even Friday (even Friday!)
I will fight 24 hours.
Be careful with the double reserve! (Be careful!)
If you fail, I'll see my blood run (I'll see blood!)
Toward the East, West, North, South, right, and left! (We'll win!)
My youth is my sin.
Exciting space-time, blazing battle.
A new journey, warriors of love.
You haven't seen anything.
Don't feel bad, but you'll be an obstacle
to our important mission.
Oooe! Tama Q.
Lamunes, what are you doing here da-mya?
Oh! I heard that your child was born.
She is the youngest of my daughters da-mya.
Daughters?
What's going on? Who is he?
Papa, papa.
Wow... you look very busy.
What's the reason for your visit da-mya?
We're passing through with Da Cider,
but we want to go unnoticed.
I want you to come with me.
Has something happened da-mya?
Papa, is he Lamunes?
The one from the legend...
The hero who committed so many blunders?
What are they saying?
I can't go, mya.
Why not, Tama Q?
I have a family now, da-mya,
and I can't leave without a reason, mya.
Don't tell me no; you have to come.
Don't take our papa away.
—Let him go. —We won't allow it.
Ah, alright, alright.
What are we going to do, Da Cider?
Well, I guess we have to go alone.
But we don't have transportation.
That's not a problem.
Ahhh...
What was that?
What was all that?
I think I'm hungry.
Thief, thief!
Don't take my money.
That engine sound...
By any chance...
The engine is in good condition.
Let the takeoff of the aluminum whale begin.
Why are they taking it away?
Who the hell dares to rob us?
That's strange. It doesn't look like it was forced open.
Hebi Metaco.
Note: A pun between serpiente (hebi) and Heavy Metal.
Who did this to you?
My dear, my dear did this.
Da Cider did?
He did it along with Lamunes.
Lamunes, why would Lamunes do that?
It's because of this.
Please, we are at the Puff Puff Palace.
Come help us.
We won't disappoint you.
What does this mean?
Lamunes, this might be a very difficult journey.
Remember, we have to keep it a secret,
especially from those two.
You can count on me; not a word will come from me.
Alright, one last farewell to Castle Arara.
The aluminum whale moves at full speed
towards the Ura Ura Valley.
Let's go. —I feel full of energy and eager.
What's wrong with those two?
Then they're going to see those two.
Doesn't it seem too strange?
I won't forgive you, you'll see what I have for you.
I have a sweet surprise for him too.
You won't escape.
Let's chase them.
The two of them could take it easy.
Let's go.
Let go of me...
I don't want to leave my family, da-mya.
Papa, papa, bring our father back.
Stop making so much noise!
Miruku, my children are not at fault.
Seyrom. —Assam.
Teacup.
Sweet wine.
Princesses at your service.
Are you in danger?
Hurry, we need some horses
—To make a carriage.
Ah! How come?
But we are guardian warriors;
however, they use us for anything,
as if we were chopsticks.
I'm sorry, guys, but we wouldn't do it
if it weren't urgent. Excuse us.
Well, I know you mean it from the heart.
What are you saying?
Okay, okay. Then direct the Giant Ship 320
at full speed to the castle's exit.
I'm going to get my revenge, Lamunes.
Da Cider, you'll see what I'll do
when I catch you.
The dawn light floods my eyes,
bright eyes like the sunlight.
Gold-chan and Silver-chan are waiting for me.
What's wrong with you?
Have you not heard the wonderful wordplay
I just said?
Note: Da Cider is addicted to creating puns.
Which words are you talking about?
I'll tell you again,
so listen closely!
Alright, Da Cider, but can I drive too?
What are you saying? Of course not!
Look over there.
Except for me, there is no man
who can steer that helm.
Ha! I can do it too.
Don't go near the helm again.
You always cause the conflicts between the two.
What did you say?
What's wrong with you?
It's always your fault, because of your stupidity.
—What are you saying? It's all your fault.
Do you think I'm scared of you?
$&%$#$, &%4%&, $&%$#$.
Move aside, Lamunes.
You do it.
What have you done, what have you done!
—I could say the same to you.
You started it all.
—But it was your fault.
What are you saying?
Do you want to fight or what?
Hey, you two, wait a moment.
Does this path lead to the Ura Ura Valley?
Well, you see...
Brother, we're definitely lost.
Remember, we have to leave.
We can't let others get there first.
This can't be.
Those two...
Everything will be fine, brother.
Gold-chan and Silver-chan are waiting for us.
Oh, you're right, there's nothing to worry about.
There's no one in the world who can defeat us.
I see, we're not the only ones
going to the Puff Puff Palace.
That means we'll have company.
Ha, they're still waiting.
Let's go!
We'll have to leave in this.
Um, what is this?
It's a famous relic.
The Sky Propulsion Dragon!
Full speed ahead!
How beautiful it is to travel in the open air.
You're right.
What a beautiful journey.
Agreed.
Let's take a break.
We need to go faster.
Yes, we can't waste any more time.
Hey, you two.
What's going on?
Men who dare to mistreat a lovely maiden
and set their eyes on others.
I swear we won't forgive them.
Who are you?
I am a beautiful warrior of royalty, fighting
for love and justice.
Seinaru Miruki.
I am Seinaru Lemon.
I am Seinaru Cacao.
I am Luna Metaco.
How lovely!
What kind of strategy is this, da-mya?
Seinaru Miruki will punish them.
What are you two doing here?
Look at me when I'm talking to you.
Wait a moment, why are you angry?
Ask yourself that.
You have abandoned your girl for another woman
and hurt the heart of that lovely girl.
I don't remember.
What did you say?
Now that you mention it, Seinaru Miruki.
What?
Please, give me your address and phone number.
Miruki punch.
Why don't you behave as you should?
What are you doing?
What?
A bit more...
I hope the wind blows strongly.
Damned.
Mikuri kick.
Lemon punch loop.
Miserable.
I didn't think they'd have the guts to come this far.
They have lost their minds, Lamunes.
We should go.
Let's go!
Where do you think you're going?
You won't escape.
Hurry up, sister.
Wait, please.
Yahoo! What speed.
Lamunes, look over there.
Clear the way!
It's those guys.
Brother, it's the two from before.
How could I forget them.
Where did all of them come from?
We need to get to the Puff Puff Palace.
Gold-chan is mine.
Silver-chan is mine.
There are too many rivals.
Idiots. - Stop. - Fools...
Keep going, don't stop.
If you stop, you'll regret it.
Da Cider, we'll have to fight.
What did you say?
Eat this.
Damn, how did that feel?
Hey, you guys, we're still here.
Lamunes, why don't you do something?
Why don't you do it?
They're as good as dead.
We did it.
They have experienced our power.
Now, we are the only ones left.
Indeed, everything went according to my plan.
Lamunes, look.
Idiot, why didn't you see it earlier?
You always blame me for the bad things.
You need to be in sync with your partner.
Why are you saying that?
Because you're a baby.
Do you want to fight?
Then let's fight.
I am Gold Mountain.
I am Silver Mountain.
Please, we'll be waiting for you...
at the Puff Puff Palace, please.
Da Cider.
Lamunes.
Gold-chan and Silver-chan are waiting for us.
Let's set aside our differences.
Let's go!
Great father of chaos.
I beg you to wait a little longer.
We are gathering the souls of powerful warriors.
Together with my sister, we will help you
fulfill your dreams.
Ah, sister, it's only a matter of time.
This world will be ours.
Do we have to climb this way?
We have to find another path.
Be careful.
I know...
Are you okay?
Thank you for saving me.
There's no need to say that.
We are companions.
Let's do our best.
We've been waiting for you.
Are you ready for your punishment?
Wait a moment.
Don't say anything.
Stay still.
What an amazing attack.
Such impressive light effects, da-mya.
These rocks aren't supposed to explode, right?
What kind of stones are these? Maybe...
Wait, wait, why are you behaving like this towards us?
Why don't you guess what you've done wrong?
What have we done wrong?
We are heroes, and we are rescuing some maidens.
Is it wrong to save them?
We won't forgive you.
Please wait, this place is a time-space bomb,
it will trigger a chain explosion.
If you exceed the friction point,
it will cause unexpected effects.
We don't care.
This area is surrounded by those rocks...
they could cause alterations to the time-space.
They have evaporated.
Where could they have gone, da-mya?
What happened here?
Where are we?
We were supposed to be in the
cave of the Ura Ura Valley.
I wonder where we ended up.
It's the castle of Arara.
I wonder what went wrong?
Wait a moment, something strange is happening.
This can't be!
Good, keep it up...
The Arara Castle will be ours.
What is happening here?
I am very confused, what is going on?
Note: They have traveled through time-space,
right to the first episode of the first season (3 years ago),
where Da Cider and Leska were villains and enemies of Lamunes XD
Subtitles by: Ander Innervideo.
Timing, encoding, and multiplexing by: Ander Innervideo.
NG Knight Ramune and 40 DX Ending 1 - Lullaby ☆ Dear
What is the waistline for?, Why?
Why is your arm long?, Why?
Like when two people hug
As if it were the law of love pulling the North Pole and the South Pole.
GOOD NIGHT, my heart
GOOD NIGHT, Good night
Like a lullaby (Lullaby)
GOOD NIGHT, before you fall asleep
GOOD NIGHT, it's not just the outfit
Touching naked hearts, ah, ah…